hi I'm John and I am one of the Nerds up
in 9000 plus back with yet another
product review today I'm reviewing the
product called hair ties for guys by a
company called the long hairs I love
this product I've always had issues with
hair ties breaking pulling my hair when
I'm taking the air tight out you know I
stretched them out very quickly usually
within four or five days it's already
failing to hold my hair just such an
extent that I'm having to twist it
around and add twists to hold the hair
in but that's when inevitably I break
the product so I've always kind of been
looking for something that works better
and this advertisement for the long hair
has popped up on my facebook and I
decided I ought to give them a shot and
honestly I've never had a better hold
they do take some getting used to
because part of the reason they hold so
well is that they're just not as tight
so when you first put one in it feels
like it's not holding your hair but it's
really holding it very well it just
feels completely differently when you
use a normal hair tie there's almost
like a pain of how it's like pulling the
hair at your scalp and that's like kind
of how you know it's good this does the
same job but it doesn't pinch like the
other ones do so I prefer these I don't
know what they're made out of exactly
but they're super high quality very very
stretchy and they return to form pretty
quickly and when I put these in my hair
I really only have to double them up
twice and they hold all day I almost
forget I'm wearing them which is kind of
cool and they come in all kinds of
different cool designs honestly it's
almost like my hair isn't up but my hair
is up so I feel a little better cuz yeah
when your hair is down you get a little
hot or it's just kind of in the way it's
just that this hair tie to me does it so
much better and here's the thing I'm
sure there are other hair ties made in
this style that do an ample job so I'm
not saying that the long hairs is the
best hair tie on the market I don't know
it's just the first I've tried like this
and I really really like how they feel
when I pull these out it just pops right
out my hair falls down to my shoulders
it's great I really can't recommend this
product enough in terms of what it
actually does for my hair or talked a
little bit about how the product holds
up because I started by talking about
regular hair ties and how easily they
break well I've had these for a little
over a month now and this one in my
hands now is the one that I have used
the most I used it for probably more
than two weeks not quite three before I
switch to this slack and yellow one but
the reason I wanted to bring this
specific one to your attention is it's
the only one that has any actual visible
wear and it's just a thread
one has just come on threaded just a
tiniest little bit but it's really
heavily reinforced so it's actually done
no detrimental damage to the product
it's not even close to snapping I'll
show you I can still get quite a lot of
pull out of it it doesn't go anywhere so
it's really superficial in time I
suspect that would get worse and then it
would snap but any hair tie eventually
is gonna break on you and like I said my
previous hair ties weren't lasting a
week generally so this one lasting more
than two weeks and only having this tiny
little bit of damage it's pretty
impressive so I don't really think
there's a whole lot else I can say about
the product itself it's wonderful I love
it also the company donates a dollar of
every single purchase two children with
hair loss I love giving my money to
companies who engage in charitable
donations
I very nearly did not purchase this
product for two reasons one kind of
pricey but actually now that I see how
long they last I don't think they're
pricey at all but these were I think
$12.99 for a 4-pack so that full up
there for hair ties you can buy the
scrunchie brand hair ties a pack of 20
or 30 or something like that for like $2
obviously these are much more expensive
but they also seem to last much longer
and because they're expensive I don't
let anybody else wear them so these are
mine so they last longer for me because
I'm the only women in my house using
them the other issue I have with this
company is their advertising and
actually when I was looking up the
reviews this is something I saw time and
time again as people complaining about
their advertising there's kind of two
aspects that get a little bit of a
negative rap one is just the whole idea
of hair ties for guys it's a hair tie
anybody can use it but I kind of
actually understand that aspect one it's
a good way to sell your product but two
there really hasn't ever been hair
products for specifically geared toward
men that had designs on them if you
found a hair product with cool designs
they were geared specifically toward
women and girls and they often were
products that women and girls would want
to wear now obviously I'm aware that
those aren't standard lots of men like
products that are geared toward women
there's nothing wrong with that at all
which is why I think there's nothing
wrong with this product
there are similar products that are
geared directly toward women so I'm okay
with them gearing their product toward
men the issue is the advertising
campaign is pretty hyper masculine I'm
really not that kind of a person
so I struggled with this product but the
more I watched their advertising the
more it sort of became obvious that it
was meant to be tongue-in-cheek but I
could see this aspect of their
advertising as a turn-off to a lot of
people as it very nearly was for me
so as I said at the start of this review
there are definitely some negatives with
this product but when it comes to what
it's intended to do and that's hold my
hair I can't find any faults it does an
absolutely perfect job and I highly
recommend these hair ties if you'd like
to try them for yourselves you can click
the link in the description below don't
forget to like comment and subscribe and
as always we have a new video for you
every Friday but if you can't wait until
then we've got more content available
right now
[Music]